so while I was saying talk about the
other one this one was coming through I
wanted to get it out right after and
this is Apple number 22 and I've called
that it takes a village so much I'm a
single parent so I don't have an X or
you've been a co-parent of any kind but
it does take a village to raise a child
and so being able to coordinate that no
matter whether you're a single parent or
you know to attend care and family I'm
sure happens finding ways to coordinate
soccer practice and so in practice and
who's doing what and what you could use
help with and how we can help each other
both parents helping each other and
people who are parents who maybe want
children in their life but don't want to
have them themselves
so aunts uncles grandparents I know
there are safety issues maybe with this
kind of an app but I'm sure as a
community we could figure out how to get
a Mize risk and maximize reward I think
in maximizing reward you minimize risk
in this case so and it takes a village
app that helps you coordinate having
raised our kids I think including what
we want our kids to be able to
experience so I don't know how to play
musical instrument
I don't have the money for my kid to
take every lesson of every instrument
take every sport take every but I would
love her to be able to play a soccer
game and see if she enjoys it to play
the violin or go and see someone play
the violin and be able to coordinate
those things for your child say hey I
have you know five-year-old who would
love to go horseback riding the club
horses can invite people over whatever
it happens to be that we can share and
help in raising the next generation for
the betterment of the children but also
our own I mean I think when you're
worried I find when I interact with kids
they're amazing they're raising indirect
with their still I mean they're human
turns out thirty minutes and they have
their own personalities and what ideas
it's amazing and so I think that if I
didn't have a child I wouldn't get to
interact with other kids as regularly
and that would be sad
there's tons of people without children
we don't want children can't have them
and to be able to ensure her children in
a certain way and have the load lessened
is it amazing aspect of community so
that is Apple 2010 it takes a village